压制:随Feng
Round and Round
Selena Gomez & The Scene
绕啊绕
You see me standing there
你看我站在那里
And act like you dont know me
却假装不认识我
But last night you were calling me
但晚上你打电话给我
Saying you want me
说你想我
Oh why you always make me feel
为何总让我觉得我是你的唯一
Like I'm the one thats crazy
太荒唐了
You feel my heart racing
你能感觉到我的心在跳
My-my heart racing
我的心在怦怦跳
Boy, I need you here with me
我需要你和我一起
We can't go on this way
我们不能再这样下去
I'm falling hard for you
我为你历经坎坷
And all I can say
我唯一能说的是
We're going round and round
我们总是绕啊绕
We're never gonna stop
从没想过停下
Going round and round
一直在绕啊绕
We'll never get where
从未到达我们的目的
We are going
我们一直这样
Round and round
不停的绕啊绕
Well your gonna miss me
你又想到我了
Cause im getting dizzy
因为我开始有点眩晕
Going round and round and round
一直在绕啊绕
You tried to pull me close
你试着拉近我
And whisper in my ear
对我耳语
You always told me lies
你总对我撒谎
I cried out all my tears
我泪流满面
I pushed my feelings to the side
我曾将这份感情搁置
But then you bring them back
但你又把我拉回去
B-bring them back
回到原轨迹
Now you got me singing
这可难倒了我
Boy,I need you here with me
我需要你和我一起
We cant go on this way
我们不能再这样下去
I'm falling hard for you
我为你历经艰难
And all I can say
我唯一能说的是
We're going round and round
我们不停的绕啊绕
We're never gonna stop
我们从未停留
Going round and round
绕啊绕
We'll never get where
从未到达目的地
We are going
一直这样
Round and round
绕啊绕
Well your gonna miss me
你开始想我了
Cause im getting dizzy
因为我开始有点眩晕
Going round and round and round
一直不停的绕啊绕
Love me or Love me not
你还爱我吗
Im starring at the clock
我盯着时钟默问
I take them flower petals off
我摘下那些花瓣
And then I watch them drop
看着它们飘落
Love me or Love me not
你还爱我吗
Im starring at the clock
我盯着时钟默问
I take them flower petals off
我摘下花瓣
And then I watch them drop
看着它们飘落
Boy,I need you here with me
我需要你陪着我
I cant go on this way
我不能再这样下去了
I'm falling hard for you
我为你经历坎坷
And all I can say
我唯一能说的是
Round and round
绕啊绕
We're never gonna stop
我们从未停留
Round and round
绕啊绕
We'll never get where
我们从未到达目的地
Round and round
绕啊绕
Well your gonna miss me
你开始想我了
Cause im getting dizzy
因为我开始有点眩晕
Going round and round and round
一直不停的绕啊绕
We're never gonna stop
从未想过停下来
Going round and round
绕啊绕
We'll never get where
我们从未到达目的地
We are going
一直都这样
Round and round
不停的绕啊绕
Well your gonna miss me
你开始想我了
Cause im getting dizzy
因为我有点眩晕
Going round and round and round
不停的绕啊绕
压制:随Feng